<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>p-hacking on Pascal Michaillat</title>
    <link>https://pmichaillat.github.io/tags/p-hacking/</link>
    <description>Recent content in p-hacking on Pascal Michaillat</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pmichaillat.github.io/tags/p-hacking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Economic Slack</title>
      <link>https://pmichaillat.github.io/courses/t1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pmichaillat.github.io/courses/t1/</guid>
      <description>This paper proposes a model of p-hacking and critical values robust to it. THis is nice and cool. Great Models and such. This book shows the following. This paper proposes a model of p-hacking and critical values robust to it. This paper proposes a model of p-hacking and critical values robust to it. This paper proposes a model of p-hacking and critical values robust to it. This paper proposes a model of p-hacking and critical values robust to it</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>paper.sty</title>
      <link>https://pmichaillat.github.io/latex/c1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pmichaillat.github.io/latex/c1/</guid>
      <description>LaTeX style file to format academic papers.
paper code &amp;amp; data online appendix Pascal Michaillat. 2020. &amp;ldquo;Critical Values Robust to P-Hacking.&amp;rdquo; arXiv:2005.04141. https://doi.org/10.48550/arXiv.2005.04141.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do Matching Frictions Explain Unemployment</title>
      <link>https://pmichaillat.github.io/papers/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pmichaillat.github.io/papers/1/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: This paper proposes a model of p-hacking and critical values robust to it. THis is nice and cool. Great Models and such. This book shows the following. This paper proposes a model of p-hacking and critical values robust to it. This paper proposes a model of p-hacking and critical values robust to it. This paper proposes a model of p-hacking and critical values robust to it. This paper proposes a model of p-hacking and critical values robust to it</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Critical Values Robust to P-Hacking</title>
      <link>https://pmichaillat.github.io/12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pmichaillat.github.io/12/</guid>
      <description>This paper proposes a model of p-hacking and critical values robust to it. This is nice and cool. Great models and such. This paper proposes a model of p-hacking and critical values robust to it.  This paper proposes a model of p-hacking and critical values robust to it.  This paper proposes a model of p-hacking and critical values robust to it. This paper proposes a model of p-hacking and critical values robust to it. This paper proposes a model of p-hacking and critical values robust to it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
